进来瞧一瞧喽 朋友们
Come on in,my fine friends.
来见证一下当代的奇迹
Come in,come in and see the wonder of the age.
一份钱看十份奇迹
Ten spectacles for the price of one.
我们的短剑公爵 还有他可爱的助手
Dare,our Duke of the Dagger,and his delectable assistant.
来啊 疯狂吧!
Roll up,roll up!
看看那强壮的大力士
Marvel at the mighty Samson,
怪物 魔鬼还有似人似怪的生灵
the freaks and phantoms and the merely fabulous.
蛇女 阴阳人 一切真实得让人跌破眼镜
Snake woman,man woman. It's all real.
噢 是的! 有些看起来真实无比
Oh,yes! Some of it's really real
有些看起来难以置信
and some of it's really fake.
但它们都无可比拟
But it's all really,
精彩绝伦!
really good!
现在 女士们先生们
And now,ladies and gentlemen,
请稍稍安静一下
a bit of hush if you please.
感受一下精彩时光
A bit of the old capital QT,
因为可爱的帕克斯小姐
because the lovely Miss Parkes
即将进入这个箱子
is about to step into this box,
然后消失在大家的视野
and vanish before your very eyes.
血腥马戏团
费雪小姐探案集
我要找芙莱妮・费雪小姐
I'm looking for Miss Phryne Fisher.
一位来自马戏团的山姆森先生求见 费雪小姐
A Mr Samson to see you,Miss Fisher,from the circus.
- 噢 - 要不然我让他以后再来?
- Oh. - Should I suggest he call another time?
不用 我去见他
No,no,I'll see him.
他是谁?
Who is he?
他是...我的一个故友
He's... someone I knew a long time ago.
山姆
Sam.
芙莱妮
Phryne.
女大十八变啊
What a lady you've turned into.
你...很显然吃了不少菠菜啊
You... clearly ate up all your vegetables.
是啊 我现在是个大力士了
I did. I'm the strong man now.
简
Jane!
你已经见过了巴特勒先生
You've met Mr Butler.
这是我的好友桃乐西
This is my companion Dot.
- 幸会 小姐 - 这是我的养女简
- Hello,Miss. - And my ward Jane.
幸会
Hello.
简
Jane.
一个幸运的巧合
A happy coincidence.
谋杀? 那你们也报警了吧
Murder? I assume the police were called.
警察带走了克里斯托弗小姐的尸体
They took away Miss Christopher's body.
问了一些问题 然后就走了
Asked a few questions,then they left.
这就没下文了
That was the end of it.
但我听说
But I hear you're
你很擅长侦破案件
in the business of solving crimes.
我很想帮你 山姆森 但我做不到
I'd like to help you,Samson,but I can't.
- 我不能回到那 - 当然
- I can't go back there. - wOf course.
你查清楚你妹妹究竟发生什么事了么?
Did you ever find out what happened to your sister?
警察逮捕了劫走她的罪犯
They caught the man who took her.
是默多克・福伊尔
Murdoch Foyle.
他因为绑架了另一个孩子被捕
He was arrested for kidnapping another child.
但他从不承认是他绑架了詹妮
But he never confessed to taking Janey.
我不是故意想重提你的伤心事
I didn't mean to dredge it all up.
没关系
Don't worry.
就算你不提我也总在想
It's never far from my mind.
杰克 我告诉山姆森你会帮忙
Jack,I told Samson you could help.
这个案子归另一个警官负责
The case has been assigned to another policeman.
- 那个高阶军士格劳斯密斯? - 对
- What,Senior Sergeant Grossmith? - Mm.
上次我们来城里就找的他
He came sniffing around last time we came to town.
琼斯先生让他帮忙
Mr Jones asked him to sort out a couple of thugs
解决几个惹事的流氓
who'd been causing us strife.
他象征性地取消了我们的抛硬币环节
All he did was close down a two-up game,
然后就走人了
then he was on his way.
他可不是个勤勉的官员啊
Not the most diligent officer in the force.
但我看来他办事结果不错啊
His results seem perfectly satisfactory.
我跟山姆森保证了 你不止愿意帮那些
I assured Samson that you don't just go out of the way
高官权贵
for the rich and famous.
实际上 那些高官权贵的案子
In fact,we generally leave
我们通常都留给你这种人
the rich and famous to people like you.
你怎么不自己无偿奉献一下?
Why aren't you investigating,out of interest?
噢 别跟我说这个
Oh,don't give me that!
这是怎么回事?
What was all that about?
费雪小姐问了一些关于嘉年华上谋杀案的事
Miss Fisher was just inquiring about the carnival murder.
一切尽在我掌控
Yeah,it's all in hand.
也许有人协助你一下更好
Perhaps you could use some assistance.
科林斯警探 接下来
Constable Collins,you'll be working
你来协助高阶军士格劳斯密斯
with Senior Sergeant Grossmith.
如果费雪小姐插手此案 你要及时禀报给我
If Miss Fisher gets in the way of this,I want to know about it.
- 是的 - 我稍后打给你
- Yes,sir. - Just a moment. I'll call you back.
格劳斯密斯什么事都不会做 他只是表面威风
Grossmith won't do anything. He just looks the part.
我保证杰克会帮忙的
I was sure Jack would help.
我不期待条子能帮我什么
I didn't expect much from the coppers.
他们会把克里斯托弗之死随便地结案
They'll chalk Miss Christopher up as just another dead drifter.
这么说你下一步
So for your next feat,
就是准备像折铁棒一样把我也给折服了?
you intend to bend me as easily as you'd bend an iron bar?
你总能看透我
You always could see right through me.
我能理解你不想回到嘉年华的心情
I can understand why you don't want to go back to the carnival.
- 你以为我怕鬼怪? - 我就怕啊
- You think I'm afraid of ghosts? - I would be.
看看你 我从不相信鬼
Look at you. I don't believe that for a moment.
全是表演罢了
It's all show.
- 那是时候我登台了 - 当然
- Then I think it's time I got in on the act. - Indeed.
桃乐西 任何有羽毛 皮草或者翅膀的
Anything with feathers,fur or fins,Dot!
都给我拿来!
Bring it all!
为什么要化妆成这样 小姐?
Why the disguise,Miss?
马戏团的人们疑心太重
Circus people are a very suspicious lot.
他们不会向外人吐露真相的
They're not likely to tell the truth to an outsider.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 你在帐篷底下把她们抓了个现形 - 是
- So,you caught them red-handed,sneaking under the tent. - Yes.
然后你的芙莱妮小姐"给我了上了一课"
Then your Miss Phryne gave me a serve.
说是因为我没把帐篷支好才给她们机会的
Said it was my fault for not pegging down the tent properly.
她激情的演讲让琼斯老板放她们进来免费看戏
It was such a good speech,the boss Mr Jones,let them in for free.
她每天都会这样 还有那个跟屁虫妹妹
Every day she'd try it again,little sister in tow.
她不太谈关于詹妮的事
She doesn't talk about her,much. About Janey.
是的 我理解
No,I'm sure.
- 太过了? - 一切刚好
- Too much? - That's just enough.
芙莱妮 不要!
Phryne,no!
他们会抓到咱们的 芙莱妮!
They'll catch us! Phryne!
没事的 来啊
It's alright. Come on.
芙莱妮
Phryne.
芙莱妮 你没事吧
Phryne? You OK?
准备好见老板了么?
You ready to front the boss?
我刚失去了头号王牌
I just lost my main attraction.
我最不想看到的事就是你也崩溃了
The last thing I need is you falling to pieces.
我不能和他一块上台 现在还没准备好
I can't go back on stage with him. Not yet.
- 那你就负责脱衣秀那块 - 不要
- Then you can take over the Peep Show. - No!
我只有这些空位了 艾米利亚
That's all I got,Amelia.
我不能专门为了你添个新职位吧
I can't just invent a new job for you.
除非你挖到了金子 否则最好走人吧
Unless you've come to tell me you've struck gold,you'd better go.
打扰了 先生 是个来找工作的
Sorry,sir. Just someone looking for work.
- 你叫什么? - 弗恩
- What's your name? - Fern,sir.
你会干什么 弗恩
What do you do,Fern?
什么都会点 变戏法 翻跟头
A bit of everything. Juggling,tumbling.
看看你的腿
Let's see your legs.
艾米利亚 现在决定吧
Decision time,Amelia.
这没什么可决定的 好吧
It's no kind of choice. Alright,
我来做脱衣秀
I'll do the Peep Show.
你来协助谢尔丹先生 我们的魔术师
You'll be assisting Mr Sheridan,our magician.
欢迎加入
Welcome aboard.
我不会让你失望的 先生
I won't let you down,sir.
你之前也在马戏团待过?
You come from carnival people?
- 从没待过 - 真的?
- Not in this lifetime. - Really?
- 可你看起来很眼熟 - 人们总这么说
- 'Cause you look familiar. - People say that.
我有个大众脸呗
Must have a common kind of face.
山姆森会带你熟悉熟悉环境
Samson will show you the ropes.
琼斯先生是在一个妓院找到她的
She was working in a brothel when Mr Jones found her.
他们把她都折磨傻了
They'd treated her so badly she'd gone dumb.
先生告诉她 她和我们一样很有价值
He showed her she had value,just like the rest of us.
她不止融入我们了 她还很受尊敬
She wasn't just accepted here,she was respected.
但显然有人看她不爽 要捆她在紧身衣里
Well,someone was unhappy enough to truss her up in a straitjacket,
再刺四把匕首 扔条巨蟒才能解气
shove four daggers into her and toss in a python for good measure.
我不知道你的肌肉帮你赚了多少
I don't know what your muscles earn you,
但看来克里斯托弗小姐存款堪比王室啊
but Miss Christopher managed to save a princely sum.
我们挣得都一样 这是琼斯先生的规矩之一
Well,we all earn the same. One of Mr Jones' golden rules.
看到这的工资了么? 和大家都一样
Well here's the wage,see? Same as everyone else.
但是这有笔大收入
But this one big payment here.
可能是脱衣舞秀的奖金
Could be extra dollars for the Peep Show.
我不觉得有人会为了
I don't think anyone would begrudge Mr Jones
一点奖金而嫉妒杀人
giving her a bonus every now and then.
这可不止是一点奖金
Rather large bonus.
看起来 还有一笔大支出呢
And a one off,by the looks of it.
她会定期付钱给雷金纳德・赛普迪莫斯医生
She was making regular payments to a Dr Reginald Septimus.
你知道原因么?
Any idea what for?
不知道 现在怎么办?
No,what now?
我想跟魔术师 他的助手还有舞蛇者聊聊
I want to speak to your magician,his assistant,and the snake charmer.
多琳 你知道帕克斯小姐在哪吗?
Doreen,you seen Miss Parkes?
- 她在洗澡呢 - 这是弗恩 她是新来的
- Shower tent. - This is Fern. She's new.
帕克斯小姐过来之前她就交给你了
Look after her till Miss Parkes gets back.
小甜心 跟着我很安全
Safe with me,sweetie.
我刚刚听说了那件事
I just heard what happened.
这就是缠在克里斯托弗小姐身上的那条蛇吗?
Is this the one they found in the box with Miss Christopher?
和一个死人困在箱子里 感觉一定很糟糕吧
Must've been awful,locked up in a box with a dead body.
宝贝真可怜
Poor baby.
半男半女 多么可怕的生活啊
Half man,half woman. What a horrible life.
这是有违自然本性的 不是么
It's against nature,innit?
我妈常说 上帝要一个人毁灭
My mum always said that God let those ones perish.
肯定是那人生来就有错
The ones that are born not right.
是啊 不过我猜上帝还是睁一只眼闭一只眼了
Yeah,well,I guess He let a few through to the keeper.
但你还是得为他们感到遗憾 不是么?
You've gotta feel sorry for them though,don't ya?
我不会为任何人感到遗憾
I don't have to feel sorry for anyone.
你说话就像谢尔丹一样 真的
You sound like my Sheridan,you do.
连街上的流浪汉都能伤他的心
Breaks his heart over every stray in the street.
她恰恰利用了他这点
She took advantage.
你是说克里斯托弗小姐?
Miss Christopher?
她每晚都枕着他的肩膀诉说烦恼
Crying on his shoulder every night for hours about her troubles.
烦恼?
Troubles?
你还真是好管闲事 琼斯让你表演什么?
You're a nosy one,aren't ya? What's Jones got you doing on the show?
我是谢尔丹先生的助手
I'm gonna be assisting Mr Sheridan.
那你就得小心点了 弗恩小姐
Well,you'd better be careful,little Miss Fern.
做好自己的本分 别管其他的事
You keep your eyes on the job and your hands to yourself.
明白吗?
Alright?
我不想惹麻烦
I don't want any trouble.
得了 科林斯 休息一下能死啊
Come on,Collins. You're not going to hell for taking a little break.
但是 先生
Ah,I don't know,sir.
我们不是该去调查嘉年华谋杀案的吗?
Shouldn't we be investigating the carnival murder?
行啦行啦 那么着急干嘛
Yeah,we'll get to it. No hurry.
先生 不如我留在这里 以防...
Sir,I think I might stay here and just make sure...
放轻松 帅哥 一切尽在掌控
Cheer up,sunshine. All things in their time.
另外 不来杯酒还抓什么凶手
Besides,it's thirsty work catching a murderer.
- 在哪? 哼? - 你们这帮臭虫
- Where is it,eh? - You bunch of... maggots!
别挣扎了 老老实实听着
Give it up! You're not listening!
你...
You...
放开...我!
Let me... go!
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
哎呦 这不是罗伊男孩帮嘛!
Well,well,if it isn't the Roy Boys!
你们两个 背靠墙站着 不然
You and you,your back against the wall or I'll start shooting,
我就一直开枪 直到有人给我颁奖为止
and I'll keep shooting until someone gives me a prize.
别管了 埃尔斯
Let go,Else.
再纠缠下去你会后悔的
Let go before you do something you'll regret.
- 他们愣闯进我家 - 我知道
- They broke into my place. - I know.
我知道他们在找啥 可惜死也找不到
I know what they were looking for. Didn't even bloody find it,did ya?
看着这个老蜥蜴
Keep your eye on the old lizard.
得有人教教这几个小子
Someone needs to have a word with these boys
该怎么对待一位女士?
about how to treat a lady.
我们可没伤害她
Oh,we weren't doing any harm.
那你们得好好解释一下了
You've got some explaining to do.
蜥蜴?
Lizard?
说说吧 不欺负人手痒痒么?
Now,was that too hard for you,boys?
那个脱衣秀的表演名副其实么?
So is a peep show what it sounds like?
嗯 秀结束的时候花点钱还能享受点额外服务
Well,on the way out,the punters can buy a little something extra.
她看起来并不喜欢这个主意
She didn't seem too thrilled with the idea.
克里斯托弗小姐在她变成阴阳人
Miss Christopher used to do it,before...
赚很多钱之前曾经这样
Made a lot of money,half man,half woman.
出双倍的钱就能买她一夜
Twice the price to have a gawk.
她很讨厌这些
She hated it.
上星期她威胁着说要不干了 他们大吵一架
Last week she threatened to leave and they had a barney.
老板恳求着她留下来
The boss had to beg her to stay.
所以说克里斯托弗小姐和琼斯先生关系很紧张
So there was tension between Miss Christopher and Mr Jones.
老板永远不会炒了她的
The boss would never have wanted to get rid of her.
她是我们最大的摇钱树 而且 我了解琼斯
She was our greatest money spinner. Besides,I know Mr Jones.
他在我孤独无援的时候收留了我
He kept me on when no-one else would have.
他就像我们的父亲一样
He was like a father to all of us.
不是所有父亲都会对自己的孩子好的
Not all fathers are kind to their children.
我可不愿为了这事废寝忘食
I wouldn't lose any sleep over it.
她是个狡猾的老狐狸
She's a slippery customer,
而那些罗伊男孩好对付多了
and those Roy Boys are a handful.
对啊 幸好你备着枪 先生
Yeah,well,it's a good thing you had your gun on you,sir.
没有枪 怎么让他们束手就擒
You can't ask a crook to wait while you go back to the station,
我准许你配枪
and get a permission note for your weapon.
不了 先生
No,sir.
是时候去搞搞那个嘉年华的案子了
Better get a wriggle on with the carnie case.
这是相关文件
These are the files of interest,
这是参加嘉年华的人名单
with a list of names for people at the carnival.
查查他们的背景 好好干
Just check their histories. Nut it out.
- 别让我失望啊 - 遵命 长官!
- Try and impress me. - Yes,sir!
好了 啦啦啦啦
OK... bah,bah,bah,bah.
- 你喝酒了? 警探 - 就只喝了一杯
- Have you been drinking,Constable? - Oh,just the one,sir.
喝一杯有利于查案啊
Helps turn the cogs apparently.
如果再让我发现谁在工作时间喝酒的话
If I ever catch you or anyone else drinking on the job,
就可以吻别你们的警徽了
you can kiss your badge goodbye.
现在马上去办嘉年华的案子
Now,get on with that carnival investigation.
琼斯会念观众给的号码
Jones will call for numbers from the audience,
然后我负责尽力扔中那个号码
and I'll endeavour to hit them.
尽力? 你这么说我可有点虚啊 谢尔丹先生
Endeavour? You're not filling me with confidence,Mr Sheridan.
我很少扔偏 弗恩小姐
I rarely miss,Miss Fern.
- 那看起来挺疼的啊 - 我之前晕倒了
- That looks sore. - I fainted.
帕克斯小姐打开箱子的时候
When Miss Parkes opened the cabinet,
我们都看到了...
and we all saw...
要是我的话肯定也立马晕倒了
Faint at the drop of a hat,I do.
真不敢想象
Can't imagine
目睹自己的朋友那副惨状我会作何感受
seeing that happen to someone close to you.
帕克斯应该给你找了套表演服装 祝你好运了
See that Miss Parkes finds you a costume. Good day to you.
事情肯定会越来越糟 不能再拖下去了
'Course it was going to go bad. Couldn't last.
简直是痴心妄想了
It was stupid to think it would.
- 就是这个 行么 - 可以
- This. Will this do? - It'll be fine.
我抢了你的活 你伤心么?
Are you... have I upset you taking your job?
看看我 哭哭啼啼的 我有什么资格哭
Look at me,blubbering like this. I've got no right.
你的朋友被杀了啊
Your friend was killed.
你哭哭啼啼也是人之常情
If ever there's a good time to blubber,I reckon this is it.
没关系的
It's alright.
哭一下又不会伤害到别人
A good cry never hurt anyone.
她在世时 我对她一点都不够朋友
I wasn't much of a friend to her while she was alive.
现在她死了 我有什么资格伤心
Can hardly come over all upset now she's dead.
真希望我们最后一次见面的时候没有吵架
Just wish we didn't have words the last time I saw her.
应该有个头饰在这儿的
Think there's a headdress here somewhere.
我妈常说 别在争吵中迎来日落
My mum always set never to let the sun go down on an argument.
她问我借钱
She wanted to borrow some money.
因为某些特殊原因
For something special.
她还差五十英镑
She just needed the last 50 Pounds.
她说不干了的时候
When she said she was leaving,
我很担心自己的钱要不回来了
I got worried she wasn't going to pay it back
于是就表达了不满
and I said as much.
她十分生气 说我不信任她
She was so offended,that I didn't trust her.
后来 我又回去找她道歉
So,you see,I went back there to apologise.
却看到他们俩在一起
And I saw them together.
然后我也不知道怎么
And I don't know what came over me.
就失去了理智
I just lost my grip on things.
说了些失控的话
Said Lord knows what.
你看见谁了?
Who did you see?
克里斯托弗小姐和谁在一起?
Miss Christopher and?
谢尔丹先生
Mr Sheridan.
原来克里斯托弗小姐和谢尔丹先生是情侣
Miss Christopher and Mr Sheridan were lovers.
- 长官? - 怎么?
- Sir? - Hmm?
我看过这马戏团里的人的资料了
I've been looking through the files of these circus people,
其中有个人有案底
and it looks like one of them has a prior arrest.
酒后闹事还是聚众斗殴
Drunk and disorderly? Affray?
谋杀听起来怎么样?
How does murder sound?
听起来像淘到了金啊
Sounds like a solid gold result to me,kid.
你在看什么
What are you staring at?
弗恩
Oh,Fern.
有的菜跟你一样恶心
Some dishes here with your name on it.
你想等到谢尔丹先生吃完
You wait till Mr Sheridan's plate comes back too,
再换水么
before you change the water.
别浪费时间了
No use wasting it.
好啦 去吧 是你查出来的
Off you go,then. You did the legwork.
艾米利亚 帕克斯
Um... Amelia Parkes,
你涉嫌谋杀被逮捕
you're under arrest for murder.
- 我准备好了 - 看到了吧
- I'm ready. - See?
她很有自知之明
She knows what's what.
这不是你第一次被捕吧 亲爱的
This isn't the first time you've been arrested,is it,love?
报纸上写过 你没读么?
It was all over the newspapers. You didn't read about it?
嘉年华杀人犯
Carnival Killar:
飞人妻子置丈夫于死地
Trapeze Wife Lets Husband Take Death Plunge.'
你从哪里找来这种老掉牙的报纸
And where did you get this,out of the Ark?
碰巧在马戏团的废物堆里找到的
Bottom of a carnival trunk,as it happens.
帕克斯小姐被控谋杀罪
Miss Parkes was charged with murder
由于在飞人表演中 未能接住自己的丈夫
after failing to catch her husband on the trapeze.
但是
But...
庭审阶段证据表明她当时突发癫痫病
during the trial,it came out that she has epilepsy,
她之前全然不知情
a condition she was unaware of at the time.
她是因为突然犯病才没接住自己的丈夫
She couldn't catch him because she was in the middle of a seizure.
所以自然被减刑了
That's why her sentence was commuted.
某些懒警官利用此案
Which makes this latest accusation
巧妙地将新的谋杀罪名也安在了她头上
a masterstroke in lazy policing.
我可能错了
I could be wrong,
但我严重怀疑给受害者穿紧身衣
but I suspect wrestling your victim into a straitjacket,
接着连刺他数刀 再缠一条巨蟒
plunging in a set of steak knives and wrangling a python
这些事不是帕克斯小姐这种弱女子能完成的
is a tall order for a woman as frail as Miss Parkes.
我猜你也已经锁定了犯罪嫌疑人
And I assume you have a theory as to who did the deed?
两个首要嫌疑人 一个是魔术师谢尔丹先生
Two frontrunners. One's the magician Mr Sheridan.
对于他和克里斯托弗小姐女性那面的浪漫关系
Very secretive about his romantic involvement
讳莫如深
with Miss Christopher's female half.
你觉得是她威胁说要将此事公诸于众?
You think she might have threatened to make the dalliance public?
有可能
Possible.
以杀人来灭口也太绝了
That's a hell of a way to keep someone quiet.
但是谢尔丹先生看到尸体就晕倒了
But Mr Sheridan fainted when he saw the body.
看起来应该不是他亲自动的手
Not likely if he'd done the handiwork himself.
晕的很是时候 但也许是装的
A good faint,like just about anything,can be faked.
然后多琳也有嫌疑 这个傲气的舞蛇者
Then there's Doreen,proud owner of the python in question.
她幻想能和魔术师发展恋情
She imagines a romance with the magician
但只是一厢情愿
that doesn't appear to be reciprocal.
所以出于嫉妒而杀人?
So... it was a jealous rage?
接着她的老板琼斯先生也有嫌疑
Then there's her boss Mr Jones.
克里斯托弗小姐提出要离开马戏团时
He and Miss Christopher argued when she threatened
他们吵架了
to leave the carnival.
推断很有意思 等你缩小了嫌疑范围再告诉我
All very interesting. Let me know when you narrow it down.
- 我想见帕克斯小姐 - 给我个理由
- I'd like to see Miss Parkes. - To what purpose?
我要检查一下你们有没有给她基本的探视权
To check that her basic visitation rights are being respected.
毕竟我是她的同事
I am a workmate,after all.
我记不清亲手害死丈夫那晚的事了
I don't remember what happened the night I killed my husband.
我怎么确保这种事不再发生?
How can I be sure it didn't happen again?
你患有癫痫 帕克斯小姐
You've got epilepsy,Miss Parkes.
山姆森提到过你吃酏剂来缓解病情
Samson mentioned you take an elixir which helps?
事情是这样的 弗恩 我...
That's the thing though,Fern. I'm...
我的确应该吃
I'm supposed to take it.
但吃了那药 我连说整话的力气都没有
But it makes me so tired,I can hardly string my words together.
你停药了
You stopped taking it?
我去见克里斯托弗小姐那晚 我发作了
The night I went and saw Miss Christopher,I had a turn.
意识清醒的时候我已经在自己的帐篷里了
The next thing I remember is being back in my tent.
克里斯托弗小姐说过借钱的原因么
Did Miss Christopher say why she wanted to borrow money from you?
- 我得帮她保守秘密 - 这点也许很关键
- I don't like to betray a trust. - Might be important.
和她见的医生有关系么
Does it have anything to do with the doctor she was seeing?
她受够了做阴阳人
She was tired of being a half man,half woman.
她想做男人或女人
She wanted to be one or the other.
医生说可以帮她 只是钱的问题
And that doctor,he said he could make it happen for her,for a price.
你们他妈的给我点公道行不行!
I want some bloody justice from you lot!
来吧杰仔 来吧
Come on,Jackie boy! Come on!
我告诉你了 他很忙
I told you,he's busy.
你们他妈的给我点公道行不行!
I want some bloomin' justice from you lot!
- 你好杰克 - 埃尔希
- Hello,Jack. Elsie.
杰克・罗宾逊 他是河这边最好的条子
Jack Robinson. He's the nicest copper this side of the river.
我是他逮捕的第一个人 你知道么
I was his first arrest. Did you know that?
真的么
Really?
- 你记得么杰克 - 我可忘不了你埃尔斯
- Do you remember that,Jack? - You never let me forget,Else.
有什么事情
What seems to be the problem?
那些讨厌的罗伊男孩 还在我的地盘附近转悠
Those stinkin' Roy Boys,they're still sniffin',around my place.
格劳斯密斯警官之前阻止了一场抢劫
Sir,Sergeant Grossmith intervened earlier on an attempted burglary.
根本不用他阻止
Fat lot of good that did.
反正他们永远找不到马仔的藏赃处
They'll never find it. That's Matty's stash.
什么藏赃处
What stash is that,Elsie?
你之前可是说你儿子马修
I thought you swore blind your boy Matthew
和伯恩斯街抢劫案无关
had nothing to do with the Burns Street robbery.
按这个逻辑
Which,by logical extension,
他也不应该有什么赃物值得小偷惦记了
would mean there was no stash to be stolen.
我是说过 不过你懂我的意思
My oath. You know what I'm trying to say,though.
你知道我在暗示什么
You know... you know what I'm getting at.
如果你立刻回家事情会更简单
Things'll seem a lot clearer once you go home and have a sleep.
- 科林斯警探现在就送你回去 - 我..
- In fact,Constable Collins here will take you home right now. - I'm...
除非你准备好审问帕克斯小姐了
Unless,of course,you're finally ready to interview Miss Parkes.
格劳斯密斯警官说
Sergeant Grossmith says that
等她紧张冒汗的时候再审问效果更好
he wants her to sweat it out some more.
他说紧张冒汗..
He says sweat...
他说什么
He says sweat what?
他说紧张是使犯人认罪的最好捷径
He says sweat... greases the wheels on the fast track to confessions.
你的洞察力惊人啊 警探
Dizzying insight,Constable.
可别让他在路上吓着你
Don't let him intimidate you on the way home,Else.
这小子还嫩得很
What,this lamb?
我问到了克里斯托弗小姐借钱的原因
I found out why Miss Christopher needed that extra money.
你会告诉我么
Are you going to tell me?
我觉得百闻不如亲自一见
I think it's something better seen with your own eyes.
我以为阴阳人是个噱头罢了
I thought the man-woman act was a con,
原来她真的是阴阳人
but she was a real hermaphrodite.
但是她不喜欢这样
But she didn't intend to stay that way.
她找到了可以治疗她的医生
She'd found a doctor who was prepared to relieve her
切除她的..多余部分 手术费要很大一笔钱
of her additional... appendage for an extraordinary fee.
噢
Ouch.
死因 窒息而死
'Cause of death - asphyxiation.'
- 是蟒蛇干的 - 不是
- The python? - No.
他是被勒死的 可能是用一根绳子
She was choked to death,possibly with a rope.
至于刀伤 紧身衣捆绑和巨蟒
Then the knife wounds,the straitjacket and the python
都是死后的雪上加霜
were all added afterwards.
过渡伤害 这是为了发出警告
Overkill. To send a message,a warning.
对谁呢?
But to whom?
我家就在这 快到了 这就是大门
My place is down here. We're nearly there. That's the gate.
我没看到那群杂种啊
I don't see the mongrels.
滚开
Bugger!
快去啊 解决他们
Go on,do something!
我是警察
Police.
如果举起双手 就不会有麻烦
If you come out with your hands in the air,there won't be any trouble.
你快给我出来 你个见不得人的蛆虫
Trouble,my backside! You come out now,you spineless maggot.
天啊 神枪手 你射中了自己的腿
Holy smoke. You've shot yourself in the leg,tiger.
又是新的一晚 请进吧
Every night's another night. Come on in.
请安静 在座的帅哥美女
Quiet,please,ladies and laddies,quiet!
在我们的短剑公爵
Complete hush,as our Duke and the Dagger,
匕首贵族 弯刀船长
our Nobleman of the Knife,
准备扔最后一刀的时候
our Captain of the Cutlass prepares to
请大家保持绝对的安静
throw his final knife.
噢
Ooh!
请把掌声献给百发百中的
Please,give your thanks to our Target Master
亚伯・谢尔丹先生
Mr Abel Sheridan!
和我们美丽勇敢的弗恩小姐
And our fabulously fearless Miss Fern!
- 欢迎下次再来 - 你肯定很想她
- Coming up next... - You must miss her.
克里斯托弗小姐
Miss Christopher.
- 我知道你们是情侣 - 那是作弊
- I know you were lovers. - It's rigged!
你们找了个托 只让他一个人念数字
The same bloke called out all the numbers.
现场有个怀疑论者
We have a sceptic amongst us.
托马斯要质疑我们!
A doubter named Thomas!
你怎么说 谢尔丹先生 给他瞧瞧真本事吧?
What say you,Mr Sheridan. Shall we prove him wrong?
不如让他亲自指定下一个数字?
How about we let him call out your next number?
- 二十 - 二十!
- Twenty. - Twenty !
谢尔丹先生
Mr Sheridan.
抱歉 刚才我不该继续的
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have gone on tonight.
我理解 真的
I understand. I really do.
以前我的爱人也去世了
I had a lover once. He died.
弗恩? 是谁告诉你的?
Who told you,Fern? Who told you this?
帕克斯小姐 今天我去见她了
Miss Parkes. I went to see her today.
她把你和克里斯托弗小姐的所有事情告诉了我
She told me all about you and Miss Christopher.
我不在乎 我知道爱情没有界限
It doesn't bother me. I know it takes all kinds.
帕克斯小姐说有人暗中给克里斯托弗汇钱
Miss Parkes said someone was giving Miss Christopher extra money.
你知道怎么回事么
Do you know why?
我真的无可奉告
I really can't say.
因为你害怕会遭遇不测
Cause you're scared of what might happen to you.
祝你今晚愉快
I will bid you goodnight.
他是你手下的一名爱将吧 杰克?
Little cherub one of yours,ain't he,Jack?
- 发生什么事了? - 我中枪了 长官
- What happened? - I've been shot,sir.
不要小题大作了 只是擦伤而已
Don't turn it into a three act play. It's only a graze.
- 这是什么? - 我不知道
- What's this? - I don't know.
他...他应该没什么恶意的
But he... he wouldn't have meant no harm by it.
我儿只是想找回他自己的东西
He'd just come back to find his stash,
于是来了藏脏处 拿完就走了
and he found it,just where he hid it.
埃尔希 你儿子在监狱里呆了好几年了
Your son's in prison,Elsie. Has been for years.
呃 那他肯定逃出来了
Well,he must have busted out.
不然有谁会留下一包我最爱的糖
Who else is going to leave me a bag of me favourite sweets,
而且还拿走了床底下的全家福呢?
take the family pictures from under the mattress?
是你儿子朝我开枪的?
Your son shot me?
严格说来 是他让你误射到了自己
Strictly speaking,he made you shoot yourself.
他... 让我射中了我自己!
He... made me shoot myself!
啊!
Aah!
如果她完成了手术
Jones had the most to lose.
琼斯失去的最多
If she'd gone through with the operation,
他就没有王牌摇钱树了
he would have lost his star attraction.
我怎样才能有机会
How would I get myself into a position
瞥一眼琼斯的文件呢?
to take a peek through Jones' papers?
不可能 老板是很真诚正直的
No. The boss is as straight as an arrow.
那他就更没什么可隐瞒的了
Then he'll have nothing to hide.
但是 假设说
But if,hypothetically,
我们想要看一看他的文件
we were to take a look through his papers,
从哪里找到呢?
where would we find them?
重要的东西都放在保险箱里
Anything important is kept in the strongbox.
能帮我拿来吗?
Could you get into it for me?
他是个好人 芙莱妮
He's a good man,Phryne.
我知道这很难接受
I know it's hard.
但好人 哪怕是圣人
But good people,the best of people,
也有意志薄弱的时候
can still be compromised.
费雪小姐住所 我是桃乐西
Miss Fisher's residence,Dorothy speaking.
他在哪?
Where is he?
我真不知道是该拥抱你 还是给你一巴掌
I don't know whether to hug you or slap you.
我有的选吗?
Do I get a vote?
解释一下为何有人传言你误射了自己?
Any truth to the nasty rumour that you got yourself shot?
恐怕传言属实 长官 这是我女友桃乐西
Afraid so. Sir? This is my sweetheart Dot.
如果你真的是个高级警官
If you were any kind of senior officer,
你就不该派这样一个毫无经验的年轻警察
you wouldn't have sent such an inexperienced young policeman
去执行如此危险的任务
out on such a dangerous job.
看来你是勾搭了一位常驻军营律师啊
Hooked yourself a regular barracks-room lawyer,I see.
事实上 我确实懂一点法律
I do know a bit about the law,actually.
我的雇主是芙莱妮・费雪小姐
My employer is Miss Phryne Fisher.
- 女侦探 - 是吗?
- Detective. - Really?
也许你应该让你雇主来弄清事实
Well,maybe you should get your employer to sort out her facts.
我可没有派你的亲爱的去任何地方
I didn't send your sweetheart anywhere.
最好把这个老酒鬼送回家
Better drive the old soak home
不然我们就要用香薰了
or we'll have to fumigate.
在她走之前我要她先戒酒
I want her to dry out before she goes.
如果你还有闲情熏香
If you've got time to burn,
或许该把注意力放到帕克斯小姐上
you might turn your attention to Miss Parkes.
我正式提醒你时限将至
I'm officially turning the clock on.
我明早一来就要知道马戏团谋杀案的进展
I want movement on the circus murder first thing in the morning,
否则就无罪释放帕克斯小姐
or I'm letting Miss Parkes go.
天知道他怎么做到的
Lord knows how he's managed it,
但是他就是莫名奇妙地逃出来了
but he has managed somehow to bust out of jail.
他是个聪明人
He's a clever lad.
我不这么觉得 埃尔斯
I don't think so,Else.
我提醒你他真逃出来了
I'm telling you,he has.
不信打电话让狱卒查查牢房
You call 'em,tell them go check in his cell.
他绝对没影了 我儿子什么样我最了解
He won't be there,I guarantee you. I know my son.
好吧 我保证
Well,I promise you,
如果事实真如你所说 早就有人通知我了
if what you're saying is true,I'd know about it.
这 坐下
Here,sit down.
好了吧? 如果真能让你睡踏实点
Right? If it'll help you sleep soundly,
我会给监狱打电话确认的
I'll ring the prison and find out.
我一直很喜欢你 杰克
I always liked you,Jack.
抱歉 你得忍受这个室友
My apologies for the roommate.
别看她现在醉气熏天
Underneath the alcoholic vapour,
清醒的时候倒是个风趣的智者
there's a lady of considerable intellect and wit.
只不过 要等她大吐后清醒过来
Unfortunately,waiting for her to reveal herself
可不是件愉快的事
isn't going to be pretty.
我最后一场十点结束
I finish by ten at the latest,
你可以在帐篷后面和我见面
so you could meet me out the back of the tent.
你看什么看?
What are you looking at?
- 没什么 我以为... - 什么?
- Nothing. I thought... - What?
我以为你和谢尔丹先生才是...
That you and Mr Sheridan were...
你以为刚才我俩在谈恋爱?
You thought that was romantic?
我们是在谈钱 宝贝
That was about money,sweetheart.
做我们这行的 不走点野路子可赚不到什么钱
You don't make enough money in this lark without doing a few extras.
小波比丢了羊羔是一首著名童谣
小波比不只丢了羊还丢了贞操
Little Bo Peep's lost more than her sheep.
这可是脱衣身表演的最佳桥段
A class act in the buff.
老板在那儿
There's the boss.
也就是说 现在他的帐篷里没人
Which means that his tent is unattended.
山姆!
Sam!
一个挂锁我还可以解决 但这...
A padlock I can get around,but this...
老板一看就知道是我我干的
The boss will know it was me.
如果我们想帮帕克斯小姐就没得选
It's our only alternative if we want to help Miss Parkes.
闻着像是某种药物
Smells like some kind of medicine.
也许是我们舞狮表演上用过的动物镇定剂
Probably animal tranquilisers from when we had the lion show.
- 未开封的连号钞票 - 这怎么了?
- Serialised banknotes. - What does that mean?
银行只会把这种钱给流油的富人
Banks only hand these out to the stupidly wealthy,
或者是拿着枪的劫匪
or people pointing guns at them.
我肯定这钱是有来路的
I'm sure there's some kind of explanation.
但可能不是你期待的那种正当来路
But perhaps not the one you were hoping for.
我要你帮我把这些交给杰克・罗宾逊
I need you to take these to Jack Robinson for me.
586934 586935
586934. 586935.
这钱显然是埃尔希儿子抢银行时候的赃款
The banknotes are definitely from the robbery Elsie's son committed.
但是它们怎么会和马戏团扯上关系?
But why did they end up at the carnival?
也许琼斯有办法洗黑钱
Maybe Jones had a way to put it through his books,
这样别人就查不到这笔钱的踪迹了
so they couldn't be traced.
有没有可能埃尔希是对的 她儿子确实越狱了
Is there any chance Elsie was right and her son did bust out,
并且逃到了马戏团?
and escape to the carnival?
请帮我接通帕克瑞奇路监狱行政处
Put me through to the Parkreach prison administrator.
我是杰克・罗宾逊探长
Inspector Jack Robinson here.
我想查一下马修・提扎德这个犯人的情况
I want to check the status of a prisoner,Matthew Tizzard.
他怎么了?
He what?
谢谢惠顾 亲爱的 你不会失望的
Thank you,love. You won't be disappointed.
我确信我不会
I'm sure I won't.
你不是要让我们关门大吉吧?
You're not going to close us down,are you?
噢 冷静点 姑娘
Oh,keep your hair on,girlie.
只有一个办法能查出
There's only one way to find out
你的有爱小演出到底有没有违反法规
if your little love show is breaching any decency laws,
那就是让我也一睹小波比的风采
and that's for me to have a little bo-peep myself.
我相信咱们可以互惠互利的 不是么?
I'm sure we could work something out together,eh?
悉听尊便 长官
Whatever you say,sir.
你来体验生活了?
Slumming it a bit,aren't you?
你来这干什么 格劳斯密斯?
What are you doing here,Grossmith?
该我问问芙莱妮・费雪小姐在这干什么才对
I think the question is,what is Miss Phryne Fisher doing here.
不是么?
Isn't that right?
这可不是一个富有的侦探小姐该来的地方
This is hardly the place for a well to do lady detective.
正义 而不是金钱
Justice,not money,
决定这个案子是否值得我关注
determines the cases worthy of my attention.
嗯 很抱歉让你失望了
Hm. I'm sorry to disappoint you,
但我已经抓到凶手了
but I think I've solved the murder.
噢 不是我抢你活了吧
Oh,does this do you out of a commission?
- 那是什么? - 作案凶器
- What's that? - The murder weapon.
恐怕你的表演得结束了
I'm afraid,for you,show time is over.
知道我在哪找到的么? 帕克斯小姐的帐篷里
You want to know where I found it? Miss Parkes' tent.
这只能说明有人要陷害她
Which only proves that someone is trying to put her in the frame.
她的杀人动机是什么?
What was her motive?
噢 这关我什么事
Oh,it's not for me to ask why.
当然 你们只想尽快结案 然后奔向酒吧
No,yours to tie things up as quickly as possible and rush to the pub.
已经有一个警察对你唯命是从了
You already have one cop by the short and curlies.
这难道还不够么?
Isn't that enough for you?
没有人告诉你玩刀很危险吗?
Didn't anyone ever tell you it's dangerous to play with knives?
你问我儿子的事了么?
Did you check on my boy?
- 他不在监狱 对吗? - 是的
- Not there,is he? - No.
是的 他不在
No,he's not there.
但还有些坏消息  埃尔希
But I've got some bad news,Elsie.
两周前马修和另一个犯人发生了斗殴事件
There was a fight two weeks ago. Matthew and another inmate.
他被送到医务室去 但是太迟了
They took him to the prison infirmary,but it was too late.
当晚他就死了
He was pronounced dead that night.
不可能的
That's not true.
监狱发了电报 但是发往了五年前的地址
The prison sent a telegram,but the address they had was five years old.
他们没有收到回信 于是简单地举行了个葬礼
So when they didn't hear back,they gave him a pauper's funeral.
这不是...
That's not...
不是真的
It's not true.
我跟你聊过我儿子吗?
Did I ever tell you about my boy?
他总是很有爱心
Always such a loving thing,
小小年纪就这样了
even when he was a little tyke.
他的眼睛充满着善良
He's got kind eyes.
他有时会跟人吵架 但他眼里满是善良
He's been in a bit of strife,but he's got kind eyes.
我能和你单独谈谈吗?
Can I speak to you please,in private?
这听起来很疯狂
I know it's going to sound crazy,
但是埃尔希的吊坠的照片里那人 我认识他
but the man in the photograph,in Elsie's locket,I know him.
他称自己为盗尸者马修亚
He goes by the name Matthias the Ghoul.
他曾经在穿插表演里上过台
He joined one of the sideshow attractions,
在那个鬼屋里 两周前
the haunted palace,two weeks ago.
我看到过他几次
I've seen him around a few times.
奇怪的是 他总是化着妆
The strange thing is,he's always wearing his make-up.
白色的妆容? 油彩?
White make-up? Greasepaint?
我当时应该闻出来那玩意的
I should have recognised the smell of the stuff.
能告诉我一个"去世并下葬了"的人
Do you mind telling me how he goes from dead and buried
是怎么跑到嘉年华里的么?
to running round the carnival?
实验室检测过了 这是动物镇静剂
The lab tested this. It's animal tranquiliser.
可能会使人致命 但是 如果没死的话
Potentially fatal for humans,but if it doesn't kill you,
副作用会使人
its main side effects are
脉搏和呼吸暂停
suppression of the pulse and the breathing.
看起来就像死了一样
So they would appear dead.
马修・提扎德付了琼斯一些从银行抢来的钱
Matthew Tizzard paid Jones some of the proceeds of his bank robbery
买来了这镇静剂
for the tranquilisers.
然后把它偷运到了监狱里
It was smuggled into the jail.
提扎德服下镇静剂 然后挑起事端
Tizzard takes the drug,picks a fight,
当别人送他到医务室的时候
and by the time they get him to the infirmary,
上演了一场罗密欧与朱丽叶
he comes over all Romeo and Juliet.
然后他被送到了殡仪馆 然后到了墓地
Henceforth he's dispatched to the undertaker,then to the cemetery.
能够从内部通过机关或复杂操作打开
这是个魔术箱 真他妈的聪明
It's a trick box. Damned clever.
- 马戏团见 杰克 - 费雪小姐?
- See you at the circus,Jack! - Miss Fisher?
科林斯 赶紧联系监狱
Collins,get onto the prison.
但...但是 长官...
But... but,sir...
查查是否还有其他可疑的死亡案例
Find out if there have been any other suspicious deaths.
我正要告诉你 长官 我给监狱打了电话
That's what I'm trying to tell you,sir. I telephoned the prison.
他们说最近
They said the only other recent death
跟提扎德打架的犯人也死了
was the prisoner who picked the fight with Tizzard.
他叫福尔  全名是默多克・福伊尔
His name was Foyle. A Murdoch Foyle.
你认识他吗 长官
You know him,sir?
费雪小姐觉得福伊尔是杀害她妹妹的凶手
Miss Fisher believes Murdoch Foyle murdered her sister.
马修・提扎德
Matthew Tizzard.
你想干什么?
What do you want?
看来你得那篇死亡报道太不靠谱了
I see the reports of your death are greatly exaggerated.
- 那不是我的主意 - 不要谦虚了
- It wasn't my idea. - Don't be modest.
他才是主谋 他说他想到一个可以出去的办法
He was the brains. Said he'd thought of a way to get out.
我只是按命令行事罢了
I just went along with it.
- 这个犯罪天才是谁? - 一个狱友
- Who was this criminal genius? - Another inmate.
他叫福尔 这些都是他想出来的
Name of Foyle. He worked it all out.
他了解这种镇定剂
Said he knew about the drug.
是他几年前从嘉年华上弄来的
Said he'd bought some from a carnival years before.
然后魔术师造了那副棺材
Then the magician built the coffins.
福尔呢? 他逃出来了吗? 他在哪?
And Foyle? He broke out? Where is he?
我不知道 我们约定在这见面
I don't know. We were supposed to meet here
但是他从没露面
but he never showed.
他在哪?
Where is he?
把玩具枪放下 你用不到它了
Ditch the pop gun. You won't need it.
真是个乖女孩
That's a good girl.
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
我是说不如花一分钟 再考虑考虑这些事
I'm just saying,take a minute to think things through.
闭嘴 琼斯
Shut up,Jones.
要不是那个变态不守规矩
We're only in this mess
我们也不会身陷困境
because your freak wouldn't toe the line.
但不就是给她个警告嘛 没必要杀她灭口啊
But you said it was just a warning. You didn't have to kill her.
那是给所有人的警告
It was a warning to everyone else.
克里斯托弗小姐做什么了要警告她?
What did Miss Christopher do?
去那边树下给这位女士挖个坟吧
Go and dig the lady's grave over by that tree.
那个变态愈发贪婪 付一次钱还不够
The freak got greedy. One payment wasn't enough.
她想要更多的封口费
She wanted more to keep quiet.
是我的错 我不应该找她帮忙
It was my fault. I should never have asked her to help.
监狱守卫会来搜你的身
The prison guards'll want to search you.
你得把这些东西藏到他们不会看的地方
You'll need to hide these in a place they won't look.
真希望我没有听你的话
I wish I'd never listened to you.
再给你挖个坟也不迟
He could always dig two holes.
福尔现在在哪?
Where's Foyle now?
跪下 费雪小姐
On your knees,Miss Fisher.
难道福尔骗了你? 他没按约定付你钱?
What,Foyle double-crossed you? He didn't pay up?
他在哪? 反正你们要杀了我
Where is he? You're going to kill me anyhow,
为什么不告诉我他在哪呢?
why not tell me where he is?
跪下 现在
On you knees,now.
不
No!
啊!
Yaaah!
放下枪 格劳斯密斯 快!
Drop it,Grossmith! Now!
你不会向同事开枪的 对吗 警探?
You wouldn't shoot a fellow copper now,would you,Constable?
我会向败类开枪的
I'd shoot a crooked one.
山姆 对不起 我...我...
Sam,I'm sorry. I... I...
走吧 琼斯
Come on,Jones.
- 琼斯会被处死吗? - 我觉得不会
- Will Mr Jones hang? - I wouldn't think so.
但是看来你得另寻东家了
But it's fair to say you'll be looking for a new boss.
帕克斯小姐 你可以走了
Miss Parkes? You're free to go.
- 就这样 - 世事难料 对吧?
- Just like that. - Life turns on a pin,eh?
- 照顾好自己 - 也没什么人可指望了啊
- Take care of yourself. - Can't expect no-one else to.
这还有个人要和你告别
And there's someone else who needs to say goodbye.
我又回监狱了 妈妈
Headed back to the lockup,Ma.
我从没想过听到这话我还这么高兴
I never thought I'd be pleased to hear that.
探长来访 小姐
The Inspector,Miss.
- 格劳斯密斯招了吗? - 福尔死了
- Did Grossmith talk? - Foyle's dead.
他的计划在没人认领尸体的情况下才有用
The plan he cooked up relied on the bodies not being claimed.
但是 他母亲得知死讯后 要求将尸体火化
But when his mother got the news,she asked for him to be cremated.
他是被活活烧死了
He would have been burned alive.
恐怕你得不到想要的答案了
I'm afraid that means you won't get your answers.
我已经有答案了
I already have the answer.
花了这么多的时间和精力来调查真相...
All this time and energy spent trying to find out what happened...
其实我始终都明白真相
when I've known all along.
我当时看戏入迷了
I was mesmerised by the show.
没注意到她的离开
I didn't notice her go.
当我注意到的时候...
And when I did...
詹妮? 简?
Janey? Jane?
却为时已晚
It was too late.
你当时只是个小孩
You were just a child.
- 那是我的错 - 不
- It was my fault. - No.
不 我不同意 我判你无罪
No,I can't agree. I dismiss the charges.
没用的
You can't.
我永远地失去了她 杰克
I lost her,Jack.
我失去了她
I lost her.
安静一下 女士们先生们
A bit of hush now,ladies and gents!
感受灵魂的转移
Feel the spirit move.
她在里面 还是消失了呢?
Will she be there,or won't she,folks?
我们能让她回来吗?
Can we bring her back,
还是已经在茫茫的黑暗中失去了她?
or have we lost her to the great black beyond?